记一下你们的假期作业
All of you, write down the homework you have to do.
课后习题第32至38题
Problem number 32 to 38 on the sheet.
然后呢?-然后？
And? - And?
-就这些？-就这？
And that's it. - That's it?
拜亚哥，我们有五天的假期
Bhaiya we have five days off.
再加点作业吧，我们能做完的
Give us some more. We will do it.
是的，我知道，所以不再加了
Yes, I know. That's why I am not giving you more.
这五天是学校的实践日
These five days are for the school's practical.
你们都好好放松一下，好吗？
All of you will focus on that and relax. Okay?
放松？
Relax?
是的，改组考试将在假期结束后的第15天进行
Yes. And your reshuffling exams will be held in 15 days of returning.
13天，拜亚哥-对，13天
13 days, sir. 13 days. - Listen. 13 days.
到时候你们再像个疯子一样学习
Then you have to study like a lunatic then.
是时候给你们的电池充充电了
Charge your battery a little.
好好放松一下，缓解压力
You won't burn out if you relax a little along with your studies.
但是你们所有人都要把注意力放在学校上
But all of you will focus on school.
乌代，你在想什么?-没什么
Uday, what's on your mind? - Sir.
这并不意味着你们就可以懒散了
That doesn't mean all of you laze completely. Just sleeping.
冷静一点
Chill a little.
你们中有多少人明天一早要去上学？
How many of you will be going to school for the first tomorrow?
举起手来
Put your hands up.
太棒了! 你们都是未来的国家栋梁
Bravo! This is the cream of our country.
非常好！
Very good!
字写得真好！
Superb handwriting!
实验报告是用草书写的
The lab report is written in cursive.
物有所值
Value for money.
他们给出的 g 值是8.2，不应该是9.8吗？
They have given 8.2 as the value for g. Shouldn't it be 9.8?
无知的家伙！
Ignorant chap!
如果你在实验室里得到9.8作为 g 的值...-是的
If you get 9.8 as the value of g in the lab.. - Yes.
那你肯定是作弊了，兄弟
Then you have certainly cheated, bro.
8.2看起来更真实
8.2 seems more realistic.
即使是A1组的学生也会从他那里买实验报告
Even the A1 batch buys lab reports from him.
为了节省8个小时花了我700卢比
It cost me 700 rupees to save 8 hours.
300卢比，400卢比是为了租车
No. 300 rupees. 400 rupees was for the scooty rental.
你那破车我只骑了两天，这还要收我钱吗？
Are you going to charge me just because I used your scooty for 2 days?
不不不，是我租的另一辆车
No, no. Not mine. The other one that I have rented.
4天只要400卢比，是不是很划算？
Only 400 rupees for 4 days. Isn't it great deal?
施万吉说我做事没有条理
Shivangi says I am not organized.
等着瞧吧
Wait and watch.
什么另一辆？
What other one?
给谁租的? 花了我400卢比? ！
And for whom? It cost me 400 rupees?!
你想让我们四个在一辆摩托车上叠罗汉吗？
You expect the four of us to sit one on top of the other?
我太机智了，我已经在车里加满油
I am so sly. I've already filled petrol in the scooty.
- 什么四个人?-你，我，施万吉和瓦蒂卡
What four people? - You, me, Shivangi and Vartika.
哪个瓦蒂卡?-拉塔瓦尔
Vartika who? - Ratawal.
- 拉塔瓦尔是谁?-希万吉的朋友
Ratawal who? - Shivangi's friend.
你在说什么，兄弟? 讲清楚一点
What are you saying, bro? Quiet. Tell me calmly.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
我应该保持沉默还是告诉你？
Should I remain quiet or should I tell you?
听着，我们有4天的休息时间
Look. We have a 4 day break.
没有辅导，没有家庭作业
No coaching. No homework.
我们一起去游览科塔
We will go on an excursion.
我另外租了一辆摩托车，这样我们四个……
I rented a scooty so that the four of us..
你，我，施万吉和她的朋友瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦尔可以好好逛一下科塔
..you, me, Shivangi and her friend Vartika Ratawal can sight see Kota.
是不是很酷？
Isn't that cool?
我哪儿也不去，我们有4天的休息时间
I am not going anywhere. We have a 4 day break.
瓦伊巴夫和我一起复习
Vaibhav and I will revise.
你要做什么?-学习
What will you do? - Study.
不，不，别这么做
No, no. Don't do it.
拜亚哥说这几天要放松，所以你应该放松
Jeetu Bhaiya said to relax, so you should relax.
哦，是的
Oh, yes.
你也会留意老师在课上说的每一句话吗？
Do you also pay heed to everything the teachers say?
不然呢？
Is there another possibility?
你的思想如此纯洁，就像我一样
Your thoughts are so pure. Just like mine.
- 我不能去，兄弟 -去死吧！
I can't go, buddy. - Like hell!
我在车里加了400卢比的汽油
I filled 400 rupees worth of petrol in the scooty.
还花了500卢比租车，现在你告诉我你不去了
I paid 500 rupees to rent it. Now you're telling me you won't go.
听着，兄弟米纳和我想复习一遍教学大纲
Look, bro. Meena and I want to complete the whole syllabus..
在这四天里
..during these 4 days.
你总是这样
You always do this, buddy.
十胜节就是被你这样毁掉的
You ruined the Dussehra fair plans the same way.
等一下
One moment.
十胜节的时候我不在这里
I wasn't here at the time of the Dussehra fair.
没错，你当时不在，现在也不在
Exactly. You weren't here then and you aren't now either.
兄弟，施万吉最近一直躲着我
Bro. Shivangi has been avoiding me for a long time.
我不想她和我分手
I hope she doesn't break up with me.
她还没准备好让下一个男孩进入心房
She isn't even mean enough to wait for another boy to enter her life..
在她和我分手之前
..before she breaks up with me.
四天之内，我想去从三驾马车到塔拉普的所有地方
Within four days I want to go everywhere from Troika to Talap..
七大奇迹之一,
..seven wonders to C V garden,
从罗陀 · 克里希纳到站立的甘尼什吉
from Radha Krishna to standing Ganeshji
那样我们就能在科塔创造许多回忆
..so that we create so many memories here in Kota..
她就不会再想分手的事了
..even the thought of breaking up would torment her heart.
是不是很浪漫，兄弟
Basic romantic consumerism, buddy.
那就你们俩去好了
So, you go, bro.
为什么让我去做电灯泡？
Why are you making me the third wheel?
有些事没有电灯泡是做不成的，兄弟
Some things can't be done without a third wheel, bro.
她不会一个人来的，大家都去她才会来
She will come if all of us go out. She won't come alone.
但是我们还要复习，兄弟
But our revision, bro.
是的，我就是这个意思
Yes, that's what I was saying. ??
-由于某些不可抗力，我们不能一起复习了-听我说完……
Due to some unavoidable circumstances we won't be able to revise. - I am talking.
什么? 什么? 什么？
What? What? What?
我们还要在4天内复习教学大纲
We have to complete the whole syllabus in 4 days.
我想放松，拜亚哥说的
I want to relax. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
带我一起去吧，乌代
Take me with you, Uday.
你不会反悔吧? 答应我
You won't retract, will you? Promise me.
不会
No.
米纳？
Meena?
我想我也该放松一下了
I think even I should go.
当然，跟我一起去吧
Of course. Come along.
- 对吧? 谢谢-明年
Right? Thank you. - Next year.
一起参加十胜节集市
For the Dussehra fair.
你去吧，我要学习
You go. I shall study.
拿着这个，给你一个游标卡尺
Take this. A Vernier caliper for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你不是让我放松嘛，我在放松
Exactly what you told me to do. Relax.
实验进行得顺利吗?-非常顺利，先生
Is the coaching going well? - Very good, sir.
一定是的
It must be.
你都没有时间写你自己的实验报告
You don't have time to write your own lab report.
不是的，先生-我可以容忍 g 的最大值为7
No, sir. - I can tolerate the value of g up to 7.
但我不能容忍谎言
But I cannot tolerate lies.
你们这帮培训班的学生不尊重学校
You coaching students don't respect school.
你是第一次来学校，是吗?-不，先生
You have come to school for the first time, haven't you? - No, sir.
- 我来过-你又在撒谎
I came. - You're lying again.
没有，先生，我来过好几次
No, sir. I came several times.
在食堂吃泡芙要多少钱？
How much do puffs cost in the canteen?
你以为我是白痴吗? 我看笔迹就知道
You think I am an idiot? I can tell by looking at the handwriting..
施乐中心的小伙子写的
..the chap at the Xerox center has written it.
这是古普塔的笔迹
This is Gupta's handwriting.
你是从神童来的，是吗?-是的，先生
You are from Prodigy, aren't you? - Yes, sir.
你不可能来自马赫什瓦里
You can't be from Maheshwari.
告诉迪帕克我想见他
Tell Deepak I wish to see him.
如果他明天不来
If he doesn't come to see me by tomorrow..
我就让所有的神童学生都不及格
..I will fail all the Prodigy students.
然后你们继续努力学习吧
Then you can keep trying for the JEE advance.
- 明白了吗?-是的，先生
You understand? - Yes, sir.
下一个
Next.
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦尔
Vartika Ratawal.
米纳，我和乌代一起去玩
Meena. I will go with Uday.
那我怎么办?-你在家里放松
What about me relaxing? - You relax at home.
他们要去哪里？
Where are they going?
去游览科塔
To sightsee all of Kota, inside out.
这真是个好计划
That is such a nice plan.
瓦伊巴夫，你坐乌代的车，你坐我的
Vaibhav, you hop on Uday's vehicle and you come with me.
打扰了，朋友们，你们好
Excuse me. Hello, friends.
我能和你们一起去探索科塔吗？
Can I go with all of you to explore Kota?
你是?-米娜尔·帕雷克
You are? - Meenal Parekh.
她是书呆子……咳咳……别带她……咳咳
(fake coughs) Nerd Alert (fake coughs) Get rid of her.
- 你好-你好
Hello. - Hi.
非常欢迎你，但我们已经有四个人了
You're most welcome, but we are already four.
我们五个人坐不下的-六个
How can five of us go? - Six.
既然大家都要去，我也要去
Now that everyone is going I shall go too.
嗨，我是瓦伊巴夫-瓦蒂卡
Hi. I'm Vaibhav. - Vartika.
小施，还是你们一起去吧? 我们改天再聚
Shiv, why don't you all leave? I'll take a rain check.
我们在路上再买个垫子-不，不，我有
So we'll buy pads on the way. - No, no. I have some.
不不，这不是月经的问题
No. No. This is not about periods.
我收到了马赫什瓦里的入学试卷
I received Maheshwari's sample papers..
我一道题都不会做
..and I couldn't solve any of it.
所以，我应该留下来准备一下
So, I should stay back and prepare for it.
- 我为你制定了整个假期计划-是的
I made the entire plan for you. - Yes.
- 现在你要抛弃我们?-对不起
You're ditching us? - Sorry.
哦! 和这些无聊的人在一起
Oh! With these boring people..
- 我会觉得无聊的-她在开玩笑
..I will get bored. - She's joking.
- 我们才不无聊-是的
We are not boring. - Yes, yes.
我们都是有趣的灵魂
We are very intelligent.
这些问题有三十分钟肯定做完了-是的
These problems will be solved in 30 minutes. - Yes.
很简单
Very easy.
- 是的，是的，我会帮她解决的
By them. - Yes, yes. I'll help her solve it.
别担心，伙计们
No worries, guys.
- 施万吉，求你了-不行，瓦蒂卡，你必须去
Shivangi, please. - No. Vartika, this is not done.
- 求你了-求你了，施万吉，求你了
Please. - Please, Shivangi. Please.
好吧，继续学习吧
Okay. Go ahead and study.
好的，那我也不去了
Well, alright. Then I won't go either.
为什么？
Why?
你到底要改多少次主意？
How many times will you change your mind for one plan?
我们又不是去果阿
We aren't going to Goa.
我帮助她学习，这对她有帮助
I will help her study. It will be a help to her.
无论如何，你们四个人刚好
In any case you are a group of four.
米纳也能帮她学习
She will study and get help. Meena will do it.
不，我要出去玩，拜亚哥说要放松
No, no. I shall go out. Jeetu Bhaiya said so.
没关系，乌代，这次我会做出牺牲的
It is okay, Uday. I shall make the sacrifice this time.
没关系-不，不，瓦巴夫，你也来
It's fine. - No, no, Vaibhav. You come too.
如果你不放松的话，你会精疲力尽的来吧
You will burn out if you don't relax. Come.
我给你腾个地方，来吧
We will adjust. Come.
不不，你们去吧，好好玩
No, no. You go. You guys carry on.
没事的伙计
It's okay, buddy.
现在只有一个空位了，对吧？
One spot is available now, right?
太棒了! 谢谢
Yeah! Thanks.
你确定你不来吗？
You're sure you won't come?
你会错过很多好玩的
You will miss a lot.
拿着这个米纳
Hold this Meena.
我们走
Let's go.
- 再见-再见
Bye, you guys. - Bye.
别紧张，我们一起做题
Don't be tense. We will do the paper.
放松
Just relax.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是瓦蒂卡-拉塔瓦尔，我知道，我知道
I'm Vartika. - Ratawal. I know. I know.
对不起，你刚才自我介绍了
Sorry. You introduced yourself earlier.
好吧
Okay.
对不起，我刚才没听到你的名字
Sorry. Actually I didn't hear your name earlier.
这就是我再次自我介绍的原因，希望你能再说一遍名字
That's why I introduced myself again hoping you would repeat your name.
你叫什么名字?-瓦伊巴夫，瓦伊巴夫 · 拉塔瓦尔
So, your name? - Vaibhav. Vaibhav Ratawal.
哦，对不起，我怎么可能是拉塔瓦? 瓦伊巴夫潘迪
Oh, sorry. How can I be Ratawal? Vaibhav Pandey.
有点尴尬，不是吗？
It was a little awkward, wasn't it?
不过别担心
But don't worry.
我们一起解决这张试卷-好的
We will solve the paper. - Okay.
你... 对不起，放松点-不，不，谢谢
You.. Sorry. Just relax. - No, no. Thank you.
走吧？
Shall we?
真是讽刺! 冷咖啡是这里最有名的菜品
What irony! The cold coffee is the most famous dish at Chai paani.
一杯冷咖啡
One cold coffee.
二杯
Two.
施凡吉，你在医学组，是吗？
Shivangi, you are in Medical, aren't you?
我小的时候也想成为一名医生，但是..
I too wanted to be a doctor when I was young but..
但是什么？
But what?
但当我长大后，我变得非常情绪化
But when I grew up I turned out to be pretty emotional.
我爸爸说医生不能这么情绪化
My dad said doctors can't be so emotional..
所以我选择了工程学
..so, I chose engineering.
- 你也很情绪化?-是的
You too are emotional? - Yes.
看看这个问题-是的，问题
Look at this question. - Yes. Question.
首先，你不应该看这个问题
Firstly, you shouldn't see the question.
什么？
what?
杰图·拜亚说要先检查问题的最后一行
Jeetu Bhaiya says to check the last line of the question first.
然后再检查一下选项
Then one should check the options.
例如，这里说，容器的温度是多少？
For example, it says here what will the temperature of the vessel be?
看看这些选择
Look at the options.
温度不能用焦耳、摩尔或卡路里来计算
The temperature can't be calculated in joules, moles or calories.
所以，选项D"25摄氏度"是正确答案
So, D 25 celcius is the correct answer.
这根本不是什么热量的问题
This wasn't a thermo question at all.
这是一个常识性的问题
It was a common sense question.
哦，是的! 我都没有注意到
Oh, yes! Actually I did not pay attention.
顺便问一下，你哥哥也在印度理工学院吗？
By the way, is your brother also in IIT?
不，不，兄弟是一个复合体
No, no. Brother is a Compounder.
什么？
What?
你是问杰图·拜亚，拜亚哥是在印度理工-我明白了
Jeetu Bhaiya. Jeetu Bhaiya is in IIT. - I see.
他在神童教书-好的
He teaches at Prodigy. - Okay.
是的
Yes.
我也应该在一开始就参加课程
I too should have joined classes at the beginning.
现在一切都乱套了
Everything is in a mess now.
别担心
Don't worry.
我会帮你把困境转变为理由
I'll convert your mess into reasons.
好的理由
Good reasons.
好吧
Okay.
我们看下一道题?-好的
Shall we do the next? - Yes.
读最后一行
Read the last line.
别靠太近
Stay in your limits.
这里有很好的家庭气氛，不是吗?-是的
This is such a good family atmosphere, isn't it? - Yes.
下次我会带我的父母来这里-是的
Next time I shall bring my parents here. - Yes.
乌代！
Uday!
你觉得让他们俩单独相处合适吗？
You think it is proper to leave the two of them alone?
你害怕米纳？
You're afraid of Meena?
我是为米纳担心
I am afraid for Meena.
你确定？
You're sure?
第一年就要结束了，但我还是不知道你的全名
The entire year is about to end but I still don't know your whole name.
米纳，你姓什么？
Meena, what is your surname?
我姓米纳，我的名字叫巴尔穆昆德
My surname is Meena. My name is Balmukund Meena.
大家都可爱地叫我米纳
Everybody endearingly calls me Meena.
你被亲切地称呼为什么?-杰姆库迪
What are you called endearingly? - Jhamkudi.
杰姆库迪，很好听的名字-不是吗？
Jhamkudi. It's a nice name. - Isn't it?
是的
Yes.
米娜尔太单纯了
Meenal is so straight and simple.
我打赌她不会下象棋
I bet she doesn't play the knight in chess.
难道不是吗？
Isn't that true?
米纳和米娜尔会是很好的一对，不是吗？
Incidentally Meena and Meenal would make a nice pair, wouldn't they?
米纳和米娜尔，米纳和米娜尔……
Meena, Meenal. Meenal, Meena.
女士优先
Ladies first.
谢谢，瓦巴夫-谢谢？
Thanks, Vaibhav. - For?
- 你帮我解决了所有的三张试卷-是的
You helped me solve all three papers. - Yes.
一天就结束了
I got through it all in one day.
我自己可能要花七天时间才能做完
I would have taken seven days to get through it.
没错，我们一天就熬过来了
That's right. We got through it all in one day.
是的-剩下的几天都没什么事了
Yes, that is true. - Nothing is left for the remaining days.
不，不，我还有事
No, no. I have something left.
我要复习教学大纲
I shall revise the whole syllabus.
很好
Good.
好的，如果你有什么问题就告诉我
Okay. Let me know if you have any problem.
好的，再见
Okay. Bye-bye.
顺便说一下，我可以帮助你复习！
Incidentally, I could help you with your revision. Yes!
我可以帮你复习
I could help you with your revision.
我很有天赋，我可以帮助任何人记住任何东西
I am very talented. I can help anyone memorize anything.
要我提醒你的立场吗？
Shall I remind you of your position?
乌代，兄弟，我不能出去
Uday, bro I can't go out.
我必须要学习，很快要改组考试了
I have to study. I have my reshuffling exam. Non sense!
是的，我没有出去，我在学习
Yes, well. I didn't go out. I was studying.
你没在学习，无赖
You weren't studying, scoundrel.
你整天都在调情
You were clinging.
跟她
Onto her.
听着，你今天教她解题了，是吗？
Listen. You sat up to teach her today, didn't you?
明天教教她睡姿-闭嘴! 流氓！
Teach her in a sleeping position tomorrow. - Shut up! Scoundrel!
这是事实，不是吗，米纳？
It is the truth. Isn't that right, Meena?
他怎么了？
What's the matter with him?
迪帕克是疯了吗？
Has your Deepak lost his mind?
他是不是不想开培训班了？
Doesn't he want to run the coaching classes anymore?
我跟他说了来见你
I told him to come and see you.
- 你告诉他了?-是的
You told him? - Yes.
好吧
Well, alright.
你告诉他我的名字了吗？
What did you tell him my name is?
我是梅塔副校长！
Vice-Principal Mehta sir.
年轻的心 -我明白了，就是你
Modern heart. - I see. That's you.
你去吧，我来对付他
You go. I will deal with him.
下一个！
Next!
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦尔
Vartika Ratawal.
“我说了”
"I said it."
“你说对了”
"You said it."
“仅此而已”
"That's all it is."
“我忍受了”
"I endured it."
“你忍受了”
"You endured it."
“但现在不是了”
"But not anymore."
再见，伙计们，再见
Bye, guys. See you.
我觉得这样不对
I don't feel right about this.
为什么? 你不喜欢吗？
Why? Didn't you enjoy?
我可以教你更好的，如果你喜欢，我还会讲笑话
I can teach you even better. I can even crack jokes if you like.
什么？不，我不是这个意思
What? No, that's not what I meant.
你想和他们一起出去玩，而我却把你留在这里
You wanted to go out with them and I kept you here.
不不不
Oh! No. No. No.
不是这样的
It's not that.
我也是很想学习的
Even I wanted to do my revision.
我还要准备参加马赫什瓦里的考试
Even I have to sit for Maheshwari's exam.
你也一样吗?-是的，真的
Even you have to sit for it? - Yes, really.
我为什么要撒谎？
Why would I lie?
-我又没说你在撒谎-没错
When did I say you were lying? - Yes.
是的，没错
Yes, exactly. Exactly.
该死！
Crap!
如果是这样的话，那也没关系，我们可以一起学习
If that's the case, then it's okay. We could study together.
是的，这真是个好主意
Yes, we can. It's a good idea. It's possible.
顺便问一下，你选了哪个中心？
By the way, which center did you get?
我还不知道
I haven't got it as yet.
很快就知道了，等我填好表格
I will get it. I will get it when I fill the form.
你还没填表吗?-没有
You haven't filled the form as yet? - No.
今天是最后一天
Today is the last date.
什么？
What?
不要脱掉外套
Don't take off your jackets.
校服不要漏出来
The uniform should not be visible.
我来点单，你们坐好了
I will place the order. You sit tight.
什么也别说
Don't say a word.
无论如何，绝对不要把身份证拿出来
No matter what, never show your I-card.
如果有人问你要身份证，骄傲地告诉他们
If anyone asks for your ID, tell them proudly.
我没有-我没有
I don't have it. - I don't have it.
我没有，叔叔
I don't have it, uncle.
先生，你必须出示身份证才能坐在这里
Sir, you have to present an ID to sit here.
为什么?-这样我们就能确认你的年龄了
Why do I have to present it? - So we know your age.
那你问我就好了嘛
So, ask me my age.
十七
Seventeen.
里面的灯光真好看?-反射
Lights were so amazing inside, weren't they? - Reflection.
我一开始就告诉你了，我们去塔拉普岛吧
I told you in the first place. Let's go to Talap..
但是你根本不听
..but you don't want to pay heed to me.
宝贝，那边也要查身份证的
Baby, they demand IDs even over there.
那他们一定是查客人，而不是查员工
They must be demanding them from others, not from the staff.
米纳，给我一支笔-好的
Meena, give me a marker. - Yes.
过来
Back.
- 谢谢-没事
Thank you, ma'am. - Never mind that.
填好表格，尽快交回
Fill the form and return it quickly.
你也是处女座的?-是的
You too are a Virgo? - Yes.
你也是?-不，我前男朋友是
You too? - No. My boyfriend was.
哦！
Oh!
你现在没有男朋友?-没有，我们分手了
You don't have a boyfriend now? - No, we broke up.
很好很好
Good. Good.
你们为什么分手?-他从不学习
Why did you break up? - He never studies.
这样不行，不学习怎么行
That is wrong. That is very wrong.
我热爱学习，学习使我快乐
I study a lot. I love studies.
我的意思是，不是所有的处女座都一样，对吧？
I mean to say, not all Virgos are the same. Right?
有些处女座的人工作努力，有些人富有同情心
Some Virgos are hard-working. Some are compassionate.
有些是情人
Some are lovers.
友情，友情……
Friendly lovers. Friendly lovers.
刻板印象是错误的
It's wrong to stereotype. It's wrong to stereotype.
你说对不对，阿姨?-填好表格，尽快交回来
What do you think, sister? - Fill the form and return it quickly.
你对这个女孩的爱让你闷在这里学习，还要教她解题
Your love for the girl made you study and you even taught her.
现在你还去填写了马赫什瓦里的表格？
Now you went and filled Maheshwari's form too?
爱情是盲目的，兄弟，不是疯狂的
Love is blind, bro, not insane.
对吧，米纳？
Right, Meena?
你每天都带他去什么地方？
Where have you been taking him every day?
我想明年应该还会再见到你的
I guess I will see you again next year.
不，不，先生..
No, no. Sir..
我一定来参加期末考试
..I shall come for the final exam.
你会来吗?-当然
You will come? - Certainly.
当然?-当然
Certainly? - Certainly
你保证？
Promise?
我保证
Promise.
去吧
Go there.
下一个
Next.
瓦蒂卡
Vartika.
瓦蒂卡 · 拉塔瓦尔
Vartika Ratawal.
“就像一场梦”
"Like a dream."
“就像天堂”
"Like heaven."
“这个世界曾经是”
"This world used to be."
“看，现在它在燃烧”
"Look, now it's burning."
“你问我”
"And you ask me."
“我为什么不高兴? ”
"Why I am upset?"
你家很漂亮-谢谢
Your house is very nice. - Thank you.
有时候我觉得自己像是在转移话题
Sometimes I feel like shifting here.
- 什么?-为了学习
Huh? - For studies.
女士优先
Ladies first.
嘿，小子!-是谁？
Hey, boy! - Who is it?
抬头
Up. Up.
你好，叔叔-嗯，好的
Greetings, uncle. - Yes, yes. Okay, okay.
你不能进来
You cannot come in.
为什么?-这个出租屋是女生的
Why? - This PG is for girls.
我昨天让你进来了
I allowed you yesterday.
我还以为你是她哥哥呢-叔叔！
I thought you must be her brother. - Uncle!
我不是她哥哥-所以我才不让你进来！
I am not her brother. - That's why I say, out!
叔叔，你把我当成她的男朋友了，是不是？
Uncle, you are confusing me for her boyfriend, aren't you?
不，我们是好朋友-走! 离开这里！
No. Close friend. - Go! Get out of here!
这什么人啊? 他在公开场合叫我兄弟
What kind of an uncle is he? He is publicly calling me brother.
你哥哥会生气的-快点! 走吧！
Your brother will be offended. - Come on! Get going!
喔！
Whoo!
请等一下，先不要进来
One moment. Don't come inside. Please. Please.
你的房东阿姨在这儿，不会有问题吧？
Your aunty won't have a problem here, will she?
不，不，阿姨会有什么问题呢？
No, no. What problem would aunty have?
乌代每天都把施万吉带到这里
Uday brings Shivangi here every day.
我第一次带女孩来-什么？
I have brought a girl with me for the first time. - What?
我是说朋友，朋友-是的
I mean friend. Friend. - Yes.
你在瞎操心，让我进来吧
You are needlessly worrying. Let me come in.
不! 不! 不! 不! 别进来，就两分钟，求你了
No! No! No! No! Don't come in. Two minutes. Please.
我见过更脏的房间
I have seen dirtier rooms.
你每天都洗澡，对吧? 这就够了
You shower every day, right? That will suffice.
嗒哒！
Ta-dah!
请坐
Please.
那么，我们今天要研究引力
Yes. So, we shall study gravitation today.
引力
Gravitation.
万有引力非常的神奇
Gravitation is such a nice thing.
万有引力有一种美丽的香味
Gravitation has a beautiful fragrance.
两个未知的身体互相吸引
The attraction of two unknown bodies for each other.
生活在彼此的周围
Living their lives around each other.
一圈又一圈
Round and round.
瓦伊巴夫
Vaibhav.
我们能放弃引力吗？
Can we ditch gravitation?
为什么?-我的力学很弱
Why? - I am very weak with SHM.
所以，可以吗？
So, can we do that first?
好的好的，当然了，我知道力学的
Yes, yes. I know it. Why wouldn't I know SHM?
力学非常简单
SHM is very easy.
我知道-但是我什么时候说你不懂力学？
I know it. - But when did I say you don't know SHM?
没有，你没说过
Exactly. Exactly. You didn't say that. You didn't say that.
力学
SHM.
哦，糟糕! 哦，不! 到我锻炼的时间了
Oh, crap! Oh, no! It's time for my exercise.
糟糕糟糕！
Oh, crap! Crap!
我不管你在做什么，你怎么能不接我的电话呢？
I don't care what you were doing. How could you not answer my call?
首先，你不用学习，你只是到处闲逛
Firstly, you don't study. You just wander off anywhere.
宝贝，别喊，会有人听到的
Baby, don't yell. Someone will hear you.
为什么我不能喊？
Why shouldn't I yell?
为什么？
因为我会改过自新，我会改变
Because I will mend my ways. I will change.
我也会学习，事实上，我正在学习
I will study too. In fact, I am studying.
力、向量、平衡、化合物、复合
Force. Vector. Equilibrium. Irrational. Compound. Complex.
你好
Hello.
兄弟，你知道我和施万吉在一起，对吧？
Bro, you know I'm out with Shivangi, don't you?
那你为什么现在给我打电话? 你破坏了一个浪漫的时刻
Then why are you calling me now? You spoiled a romantic moment.
对不起，伙计，瓦蒂卡来了-哦！
I'm sorry, buddy. Vartika has come. - Oh!
避孕套在H·C·维尔马的书里，第二章，半导体
Condoms are kept in H.C.Verma, part 2, the semi-conductors.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
我要非学院的登录密码
I want the login password for Unacademy.
- 你做不到的，孩子-我也不想做
'You won't be able to do it, boy.' - I don't want to do it either.
我们只是朋友，好吗
We are just friends, okay.
密码就是"密码"，小写全拼
Its the password. All small.
他一定能考上印度理工
He's a true IITian.
为什么？
Why?
到死都是处男
He'll die a virgin.
亲爱的同学们，让我们来看看今天的弹簧座系统
My dear students, let's have a look at the spring block system today.
这是块，这是弹簧，如果我把弹簧拉长
This is the block. This is the spring. If I elongate the spring by..
瓦伊巴夫!-好的，马上来，最后两个
Vaibhav! - Yes, I'm coming. Last two.
吸气
Breathe in.
呼气
Breathe out.
你真的太有用了
This is very useful at the last minute.
谢谢你，兄弟
Thank you, bro.
我们全都做出来了
We did it all.
明天就要考试了，我不怕
The exam is tomorrow and I am not afraid.
我的意思是，不那么怕了
I mean, not that much.
我只要看一下那些末日笔记就完事了
I just have to read the doomsday notes and I'm done.
什么笔记?-末日笔记
What notes? - Doomsday.
等等
Hold on.
这歌，最后一分钟的复习
These. For last minute revision.
它包含了每一章的概述
It contains the overview of each chapter.
哦! 我也做了这个，等等，我给你看
Oh! I too have made this. Wait. I'll show you.
所有的考点和时间
All the topics and time.
你可以通过非学院的应用程序在任何章节观看它
You can watch it on the Unacademy app from and to any chapter.
你一直看这个流量够用吗?-没事
Don't you lose data if you check it all the time? - No.
我离线下载的-哦，我明白了
I download it offline. - Oh, I see.
你已经把这么大的内存都装满了?-是的
You've filled up such a big register. Seriously? - Yes.
你为什么对马赫什瓦里的入学考试这么紧张？
Why are you so tense for Maheshwari's entrance test?
因为很难
Because it is tough.
是的，没错，但是我们已经都复习到位了
Yes, that it is, but we have covered everything.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
事实上
Actually
我的哥哥是马赫什瓦里最好的一组
my brother was in Maheshwari's top batch.
哦!-所以，我觉得至少如果我能进入马赫什瓦里.
Oh! - So, I felt at least if I make it to Maheshwari..
就能获得考上印度理工学院的信心
..I will gain confidence that I can get to IIT..
但我觉得我没有任何机会
..but I did not feel I had any chance.
你知道我在这四天里学到的东西比一年里学到的还要多
You know I've learned more in these 4 days than I did through the year.
我开始觉得自己像个白痴
I had starting feeling like an idiot.
谢谢你帮我重建自信
Thanks for restoring my confidence.
你为什么不早点来科塔？
Why didn't you come to Kota earlier?
我们本可以早点成为朋友的
We would've become friends earlier.
是的
Yes.
我能说什么呢？
What can I say?
你不告诉我们也没关系，但一定要告诉她
It's okay if you don't tell us, but make sure you tell her.
一旦明天考试结束，天知道你什么时候能再见到她
Once the exam gets over tomorrow, Lord knows when you'll see her again.
环境已经创造好了，兄弟，向她表白吧
The mood is set, bro. Propose to her.
听着，明天是个好日子，对吧? 拿着这个
Listen. Tomorrow is an auspicious day, right? Take this.
穿得精神点
Go in style.
“就像一场梦”
"Like a dream."
“就像天堂”
"Like heaven."
“这个世界曾经是”
"This world used to be."
“看，现在它在燃烧”
"Look, now its burning."
“你问我”
"And you ask me."
“我为什么不高兴? ”
"Why I am upset?"
“事情不会再按你的方式发展了”
"Things won't work your way anymore."
“说吧”
"Say it."
“此时此刻”
"Now and here."
“爱情万岁”
"Long live love."
哥，有酸奶吗?-有
Bhaiya, you have yogurt? - Yes, you can have yogurt.
在那
Take it from there.
还有..
And...
糖?-有的
Sugar? - We have sugar too. There you go, bhaiya.
多少钱?-三十卢比
How much? - Thirty rupees, bhaiya. 30.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这是什么？
What is this?
今天是个好日子
Today is an auspicious day.
这能带来好运-哦，好吧
So, this is auspicious. - Oh, okay.
如果你吃酸奶，紧张情绪就会消失
If you eat yogurt your nervousness will disappear.
你也吃，你也要考试
You eat it too. You too are sitting for the exam.
是的，哦! 我也要考试
Yes, oh! I too am sitting for the exam.
我们现在该怎么办?-我不知道
What do we do with this now? - I don't know.
我们把它涂在头发上吧
Let's apply it on our hair.
它会使头发有光泽-恶心！
It will make the hair lustrous. - Gross!
我开玩笑的
I'm joking.
我不是告诉过你我没那么无聊吗?-是的
Didn't I tell you, I'm not that boring? - Yeah.
我们吃完吧-好
Let's finish it. - Yeah.
“爱情万岁! ”
"Long live love!"
“上面写着... ..
"It is written..
用红墨水写的
..in red ink."
“我的动机是叛逆的”
"My motives are rebellious."
“看，现在它在燃烧”
"Look, now it's burning."
“你问我”
"And you ask me."
“我为什么不高兴? ”
"Why I am upset?"
“事情不会再按你的方式发展了”
"Things won't work your way anymore."
“说吧”
"Say it."
“现在和这里”
"Now and here."
“爱情万岁”
"Long live love."
“爱情万岁! ”
"Long live love!"
“我的梦想... ..
"My dreams..
和梦想联合起来，你要知道”
..have united with dreams. Know that."
“我的动机... ..
"My motives..
动机是一致的，要知道”
..have united with motives. Know that."
“爱情万岁! ”
"Long live love!"
不是印度理工学院，我要参加 sat 考试，我想去美国
Not IIT. I will sit for the SATs. I want to go to US.
康奈尔，耶鲁，哈佛，哥伦比亚
Cornell, Yale, Harvard, Columbia. One of these.
什么？
What?
我叔叔在那边，他叫我去的
My uncle is over there. He told me to come.
那你为什么在这里学得这么辛苦？
Then why are you working so hard over here?
为了知识，多学有没有坏处
For knowledge. Knowledge doesn't get wasted.
乌代，带我一起走
Uday, take me with you.
这个世界上没有人会永远呆在一个地方
Nobody in this world stays put in one place.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
- 我已经在等结果了-是的
I'm already eager for the results. - Yes.
不过需要两个星期-是的
It will take two weeks though. - Yes.
好的，再见
Okay, then. Bye.
再见
Bye.
See you.
瓦蒂卡-嗯
Vartika. - Yes.
怎么了
Yes.
瓦蒂卡，你... 你会早点睡觉，是吗？
Vartika you... you will go to bed early, won't you?
- 平静地-是的
Peacefully. - Yes.
你也是
You too.
是的，我也是
Yes. Me too.
好吧，晚安-晚安
Okay, then. Goodnight. - Goodnight.
保持联系-好的
Stay in touch. - Yes.
该死！
Crap!
瓦伊巴夫!-瓦蒂卡
Vaibhav! - Vartika.
我们可以开始12年级的教学大纲了吗？
Can we begin the syllabus for the 12th?
是的，当然可以
Yes, we could do that.
- 明天-明天
Tomorrow. - Tomorrow.
酷
Cool.
- 晚安-晚安
Goodnight. - Goodnight.
再见
Bye.
“我说，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意”
"If she agrees."
“如果她用眼睛唱摇篮曲”
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
“我会飘进梦里”
"I will float into dreams."
“阻止我”
"Stop me."
“我说，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意见面... ..
"If she agrees to meet ..
然后花点时间
and spends a few moments."
“我会表达我的感受”
"I'll express my feelings."
“请阻止我”
"Please stop me."
“哦，请阻止我”
"Oh please stop me."
“但请不要阻止我们... ..
"But please don't stop us..
. . 当我们迷失在这种方式.
..when we are lost in this manner..
在我们的小世界里
..in our small world."
“你为什么要阻止我们? ”
"Why would you stop us?"
有时在我们忙碌的生活中，找到了爱情，但爱情却离开了我们
Sometimes in our busy lives we find love, love leaves us.
或者永远坚持下去
or holds on forever.
这首浪漫的歌触动了你的心灵
This romantic track to touch your hearts.
在科塔七大奇迹不够用
The seven wonders that are made in Kota are less.
你是第八大奇迹，我的爱人
You are the eighth wonder, my love.
再见
Bye.
爱你，想你，么么么
Love you. Miss you. Take care.
这将持续六个月
This will last another six months.
伙计，我应该好好学习的
Buddy, I should have studied.
很多时间被浪费了，因为我想放松
A lot of time was wasted because I wanted to relax.
甚至学习也可以很放松，兄弟
Even studies can be very relaxing, bro.
你只是需要一个合适的搭档
You just need the right partner.
“你能想象... ..
"Can you imagine..
当我们迷失的时候
..when we are lost..
在星空中
..in the stars."
“你怎么找到我们? ”
"How would you find us?"
“我说，嘿”
"I said, hey."
“如果她同意”
"If she agrees."
“如果她用眼睛唱摇篮曲”
"If she sings a lullaby with her eyes."
“我会飘进梦里”
"I will float into dreams."
“阻止我”
"Stop me."